Come on. Can I talk to you?
Prophecy Time
How are you?
I am fine, sir.
I hope if I talk to you, you will not be annoyed?
No, sir.
Are you here for deliverance?
Yes, sir.
Because you are a drunkard.
As beautiful as you are, each time you finish and people see you drunk,
they always pity you.
Yes, sir.
There was a time you were half-naked.
They had to pull you out of the gutter.
Yes, sir.
There was a time they abused you when you took this.
Prophecy Time
She didn't know that they abused her; it was when she woke up,
she saw sperms on her body.
Almost five people abused her.
Prophecy Time
It is a curse.
Man of God, what you said is true.
My own problem is that when I drink, I aIways beat up my children.
When you drink, you always beat up your children?
Yes, sir.
All the money I was having, I would spend it.
Sometimes, I would drink for one week without stopping.
I would not eat anything.
Every day, I would smoke four packets of cigarettes.
When I finished doing it, I would start regretting.
I don't even know what got me into doing that -
either I would be too happy or too sad and I would start.
Lately, I have been wanting to commit suicide for no reason.
Look here!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
You are free.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Shall we rise up.
What shall we say unto the Lord
All we have to say is thank You Lord
Thank You, Lord
Praise the Lord! Children of God, Emmanuel!
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mrs. Sandra Shaw.
This is my husband and my two children.
I want to thank God for my life and my family.
Sunday was the first time I had been to The SCOAN.
I had never seen the prophet before in my life.
When he was giving prophecies, he came to my seat and called me out
and said to me, "You are a drunkard".
I was shocked and embarrassed but something in me said,
"You know why you came".
I had been to places but they had never told me that I was a drunkard before.
They had always said that I had a spiritual husband
but nobody had ever told me my problem; I knew my problem.
So, when the man of God said that, I said, "Thank You, Lord" in my heart,
that, that was my final bus stop.
I said, "Yes, sir".
He said that he hoped I would not be offended if he told me my problem.
I replied that with all due respect he should please say it
because everybody knew that the only problem I had was that of drinking.
I was not ashamed to say that I drank because I had been praying for deliverance.
Come on. Can I talk to you?
Prophecy Time
How are you?
I am fine, sir.
I hope if I talk to you, you will not be annoyed?
No, sir.
Are you here for deliverance?
Yes, sir.
Because you are a drunkard.
The man of God said that there was a time I was drunk
and found myself in a gutter and that I had been abused but did not know.
There was a time they abused you when you took this.
Yes, sir.
Prophecy Time
She didn't know that they abused her; it was when she woke up,
she saw sperms on her body.
Almost five people abused her.
Prophecy Time
It is a curse.
In my heart, I said yes.
In my heart, I knew that once that thing happens...
I have gotten drunk and after that prepared poison for my kids to drink.
The only thing that saved my kids was that on that day, a friend took them out
and refused to release them to me.
I abused her; I was stoning her gate.
I said I would cause alarm but she refused to release them.
If she would have released them, they would have eaten the poison and died.
Especially my first son, if I got drunk, I would hate him for no reason.
I would beat him for three days, injure him. I would carry a knife and a bottle.
Even to see my husband, I would get sad.
It all started after I had my second son, Daniel, twelve years ago.
Three weeks after I had given birth to him, my husband bought me a car
and I had a party.
The following day, I had a dream.
In that dream, I was naked and mad, wandering around the streets.
I woke up and I didn't understand the dream.
Then, I was not a Christian; I did not go to church.
I didn't consider the dream; I never even shared it with anybody.
The next day, I realised that I started bleeding.
For one year, I had my period, nonstop.
I went to the clinic and they told me that maybe I had the 'baby blues'.
Each day, I would be sad.
I would drink in a way that if you came to my house, you would never know
that I was drinking because I did it secretly.
In a day, I could consume 7-8 packets of cigarettes.
Each time I smoked and drank, something would tell me
to just enter my car and drive away.
I would go out without knowing where I was going.
Afterwards, I would not even remember that I drove somewhere.
Sometimes, at midnight, 2 AM, 4 AM or 6 AM, I would be driving.
I would wake up at 10 AM and find myself resting on the steering wheel.
I would find myself in an unknown location.
Sometimes, I would drive to the beach, thinking I would drive into the sea.
I once tried it in Ghana and when I was close to the water, the car engine died.
It wouldn't start and then, people started gathering.
Does it mean when you are driving, you park in the midnight and sleep inside the vehicle?
I wouldn't know I had been driving, how the car stopped or where I was.
And you would sit inside it there?
Yes, sir.
Who would now come to wake you up inside in the vehicle?
By the time people would wake me, they would have stolen my phones,
my bag and taken everything in the car.
In 2009, I had a serious accident.
Under six years, I have had 8 serious accidents that almost took my life
but nothing happened to me; the air bag would come out.
In those eight accidents, my car was destroyed beyond repair.
The airbag would come out and nothing would happen to me.
In 2009, I had a very serious accident.
That accident was the reason I later relocated to Ghana.
The accident took place in Port Harcourt.
In that accident, the guy in the vehicle that I had hit, they had to amputate his leg.
At that time, my husband and I had already started having problems
because of the drinking; he was no longer happy with the marriage.
The family of the guy had to fly him out and I had to pay for it.
I had to sell my property of almost $100,000 to be able to send him
to USA for medical treatment.
Anytime I got drunk, I would fight my husband.
Sometimes, I would pick up the phone and call his employers.
and started threatening them that if they didn't fire him, I would kill them,
destroy the company house they had given us and fight all the workers.
The next day, they would call him and tell him that they were happy with him
but that they couldn't take this.
They would say, "Our company is well respected, so we are sorry but
we can no longer employ you".
They said that if he wanted to work for them, they would have to transfer him
to a place far from me and that as long as he stayed with me,
he couldn't work for them.
They would sack him. Every month, he would lose his job because of me.
Still yet, he would stay with me.
He lost all the friends he had made
since he came to this country, 35 years ago.
Nobody talks to him, nobody sits with him because he is still married to me.
They would say, "We don't know why you're still with this lady that always disgraces you".
The money he earned every month,
sometimes up to $30,000, he would give me.
I can't account for any of it.
All the money he had worked for, for the past 15 years, I would spend it.
I wouldn't even know what I used it for because of the alcohol.
Mrs Sandra Shaw - Prophecy Confirmation
Last Sunday, the man of God called me out and told me my problem.
For over 15 years, I had been looking for a solution.
I got tired of looking for a solution.
I told God when I came on Sunday that I didn't want to enter 2014
with this disease or I would kill myself.
I prayed and fasted before I came.
I told God that it was my last bus stop.
I thank God for answering my prayer
because I never believed I would survive this year.
I told my God that I didn't want to enter next year with this shame.
Anywhere I went, people didn't want to have anything to do with me.
Nobody would want to sit with me.
Everyone that was supposed to respect me would disrespect me
because I was an alcoholic.
I don't find joy in doing it.
Sometimes, I think, and regret.
I lost the respect from my children because of my character.
After my deliverance, for the past week, I have been in the presence of the Lord.
I have not felt that pain in my heart nor had the urge to drink or smoke.
I bless God!
Mrs Sandra Shaw & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
You've listened to that. Let's hear that part again.
After that deliverance, the urge to smoke, to drink - tell us!
I noticed these, every week.
The church I attended in Ghana has a programme on Tuesdays, Fridays and Sundays.
On Mondays, I would drink so that on Tuesdays, I could not go to church.
Then I would drink on Tuesdays and Wednesdays.
On Thursdays, I would not drink.
During the early mornings between 2am and 3am on Thursday mornings,
something would talk to me, "Have a cigarette; have a drink".
I would have one drink and it would seem as if something had stepped out
of me and something else had entered.
I would drink on Fridays and Saturdays.
On Sundays, I wouldn't be able to go to church.
It would always happen and in a week, I would have three crises.
I could wake up happy but then I would start drinking and playing music
or I would wake up very sad that there would be nothing anybody could do to please me.
The only people I wanted to hang out with were those who drank.
If you meant me well, I would not want to be around you.
After my deliverance on Sunday, that night I dreamt that I saw the man of God.
The clothes the man of God wore when I saw him on Monday night
were the same clothes he wore in my dream on Sunday night.
I was climbing a step.
As I was climbing the step, the man of God was coming out.
He said to me, "My daughter, keep climbing; don't look back.
Just keep going; don't look back. Just go".
Mrs Sandra Shaw
Prophecy Confirmation
I woke up from that dream and found myself in the camp here. I said, "God, thank You.
Thank You, Jesus!" because I have always said, when a man of God prophesies to you,
that there is solution to your problem
and when you see him in the dream, indeed you are healed.
And I said to myself, I even told the people around me that I know that I am healed.
I feel free! So, since that Monday, the pain...
Previously, I was scared to go home or anytime it was almost morning, I would be scared
because I knew that pain would come with full force.
But since Monday, I have not had any pain in my heart or the urge to drink.
Each time I think of drinking or smoking, it disgusts me.
Mrs Sandra Shaw & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
What message do you have for the whole world?
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Viewers all over the world, I want you to know that there is God.
In any situation you are passing through, just believe in God.
Let no human being tell you that he will take you here or there.
I went to some places and was told that if I drank the root once,
that once I drank it, if I saw alcohol, I would throw up.
But to my greatest surprise, when I went to such places, my problem became worse than before.
I want you to know that God is God, and He is the only One who will save you.
Whoever is having the problem I once had,
I want you to pick up the courage to come down here, because God is here.
I didn't even believe that God was here.
Previously, when people would advise me to come to T.B. Joshua,
I would reply that they should not talk about it.
I did not want to go where they cast one out and put 100.
For 12 years, I had been looking for a solution. This is the first man of God
who has told me my problem, and hit where it had been happening.
I bless God for his life and family. Thank You, Jesus!
I want you not to give up; have courage.
When I was coming here, the devil was telling me that if I came, I would die.
I faced challenges. Even on Sunday when I was sitting down,
the evil spirit told me to leave.
I told God this was my final bus stop
and I wouldn't enter next year with this disease.
It was a decision I made.
So, no matter what the devil is telling you, that he will kill you
or any other thing, don't mind the devil.
He is only fighting to be able to put you in bondage.
Pick up courage and come.
Even though you cannot afford to come,
there are so many people that can assist you.
If you want, I can assist you.
If you look at me, you would know that money is not my problem.
To have money and be humiliated is the worst thing that can happen to you.
There was a time I prayed to God, saying, "Let me be poor but have my peace".
Right now, I have my peace and joy, and I am not ashamed to say it.
I thank God for my life.
Oh! I like that language. I want you to repeat once again.
That is, money is not a problem.
She said there is everything.
Tell those who believe so much in money.
Much money, money - they believe so much in money!
She said that there was a time she prayed for money to go and have peace instead.
Please start from the issue of money because when my people here hear 'money', they laugh;
when they hear other things, they clap.
You see! Nobody claps when they hear 'money'.
Mrs Sandra Shaw & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Children of God, I want you to know money is not the problem
because if you look at me, you would know that I have it all
but I didn't have peace.
It got to a point I told God to make me poor and let me have peace.
Now, I can sleep and eat. I have peace and joy.
I thank God for His mercy.
Thank You, Jesus!
By what you are saying now, shows that in the past,
you really wanted to get out of the mess - the problem - because you did not like that lifestyle.
You just did not know how to get out of it.
Tell us about that.
Man of God, for the past eight years I have been living on my own.
I had not separated or divorced my husband but I chose to live on my own
because I didn't want to cause him any pain or make him lose his job.
Ever since I moved Ghana, he has kept a steady job, except when he was sick.
I had to bring my children to go to school in Nigeria, whilst I was in Ghana
so that they could be in boarding school.
During the weekends, they would come home to be with their dad.
I saw myself as the problem.
Everyone would be happy but every time I came, everyone would be scared.
My son would not even have the appetite to eat once he saw me.
Not that he doesn't love me but he would be scared
because he knew that every two days, I would have a crisis.
Whenever I had crisis, he and his father would be the ones to suffer.
It had affected me and my marriage so much.
I couldn't do any business. Any money I put into any business would crumble.
I could drink and spend between $10,000 - $20,000 in a week.
My name is Jerry Shaw.
Sandra is my wife and these are my two children.
For the past five years, it had been hell.
It has been absolute hell because of the way Sandra behaved.
Concerning the drinking for the past five years, the more she would drink,
the angrier she would get, until she became extremely violent.
The more violent she got, the more she would turn against the children.
It is not even up to 10 weeks ago that she was visiting.
At that time, I was in Abu Dhabi.
People had to come to the house to rescue the children.
They had to take them somewhere else and hide them because of her temper.
She was ripping the flat screen TVs off the walls in the whole house.
She would smash the TVs on the floor in hot temper because of the alcohol.
This had been the same chorus for the past five years.
Before that, she had problems with alcohol but she was manageable.
For the past five years, she just turned absolutely crazy with the alcohol.
The difference I see in her this week is much.
This morning, when she woke up, she was happy and friendly.
She wasn't like before, snapping at the kids and shouting at everybody.
This morning when she got up, she was happy.
She bathed the kids and made sure everyone was okay.
The kids were terrified of her.
If you see the children, they were terrified of her.
As soon as she drank, they would run away and hide.
When she was sober, there would be no problem and they would love her to bits.
But as soon as she would have a drink, it was a major problem.
So, I have seen a massive difference today.
She is happy, expressing herself and talking.
She is happy with the kids. She came downstairs to have breakfast,
which she would never ever do before.
Now, she is doing it; so, I thank God.
Mrs Sandra Shaw
Prophecy Confirmation
Wow! You have listened to that.
I think if the Lord would anoint a minister of God especially for this issue,
because there are many people in camps for reformation.
In many homes, children of the rich, heroes, and presidents are in the camp;
because of addictions.
If I am right, let me see your hands.
This problem is all over the world; all over the world.
There is no solution.
We pray that God should anoint ministers of God that can rescue these people all over the world.
Deliver them just like our sister here has been delivered.
We want to say happy marriage once again.
I want to salute our father, who just spoke.
Ninety percent of men cannot bear what he has borne.
Mr Jerry Shaw
Prophecy Confirmation
If I may say ninety-nine percent.
Mrs Sandra Shaw & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
Listen!
I used to say that to people as a minister of God.
The issue of racism is not colour.
It is not an issue of colour.
They say, "This person is racist, this one is racist, this one is black, this one is white".
No! The issue of racism is not colour; it is a spirit.
Can you see what is happening between this husband and wife?
He was not bearing all those things because the woman was black or white
but he bore it because he has a good heart.
Mrs Sandra Shaw & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
In the world, racism is a discussion based on colour.
It is not an issue of colour; it is evil spirit in a man or woman.
I am very sure if it were a black man that married our sister here,
he would not stand the pain.
If I am right, let me see your hand!
Mrs Sandra Shaw & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
They will not stand the pain
but here is a brother from a different racial background that stood the pain.
He saw her pain as his own pain.
Imagine, if our father here had left the marriage a long time ago,
this woman would have died.
The woman is alive because the man is with her.
That is the solution.
We are having this discussion today because this man is still in the marriage.
If this man had divorced her a long time ago, we would not be talking about this today.
She needed a companion like this man, to stay alive.
She's here today.
So, tell the whole world.
Please stretch your hand.
The issue of racism is not colour.
It is not colour!
It is the issue of evil spirit!
It is not colour!!
It is not white or black or green.
Thank you very much.
Mrs Sandra Shaw & Family
Prophecy Confirmation
Rise up!
Majesty
Worship His Majesty
Unto Jesus
Be all glory, honour and praise
We'll worship You Lord.
Majesty
Kingdom authority
Flows from His throne
Unto His own
His anthem raise
So exalt
Lift up on high
The name of Jesus
Magnify
Come glorify
Christ Jesus the King
We worship You Lord
Majesty
Worship His Majesty
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world!
RV: Mel Flowers 21/03/2019